so there are these four questions that I
have been mulling over for the last few
weeks because answering them at any
level is beneficial and answering them
at a deeper and deeper level the journey
towards that is how we create individual
lives that matter and a society and
world that supports those for everyone
the four questions are ones that are
never answered
they're very individualistic very yours
are going to be different than mine and
that part of what makes them work but
I'm gonna benefit by answering them for
me and I'm gonna benefit by you
answering them for you and you're gonna
benefit by me answer them for me so at
every level we answer them we create
solutions at a deeper and deeper level
for ourselves for each other and as a
whole and these four questions are who
am I who are my people
what is my purpose and what do I need
and so Who am I the more you're able to
figure out what makes you unique what
makes you tick what your talents and
challenges are and the more we don't
restrict what that looks like for any
individual person you don't need to have
all the metrics I have to know who I am
I don't need to put you in a box you can
put your own self in a box if you want
to but the more we're able to create a
culture of being able to show up as
ourselves and accept other people
including that people can accept other
people there's definitely layers and we
don't always get along that's part of
finding our people finding people we're
gonna be able to connect to it and get
along with most of the time be able to
support each other we get to decide
whether or not we interact with another
individual but we can't hopefully cut
them off from community as a whole
because you finding your community is
gonna benefit me and me fighting my
community's gonna benefit me and you
finding your communities gonna benefit
me too and the more we restrict what
that looks like
because it's not convenient for us or
makes us feel weird and bad then the
less benefit that's gonna be because
we're better human beings and we're
connected
we're better human beings we can show up
as ourselves we're better human means
when we know what our purpose is when we
figure out the work that we would do and
will do and can do for free the thing
that puts us into flowing into genius or
just the next best fun thing to do when
we figure out because part of our
purpose is just being ourselves and
finding our people and being that person
in a group bringing up ideas
entertaining there's so many things to
be that is part of purpose and other of
us have a more structured for engineers
for doctors for people who more
overarching purpose and again me finding
my purpose is a benefit to me but you
finding your purpose is to accession we
all get to benefit off of the genius and
flow that we have locked together and
the fourth question is what do I need
and we all have very similar needs in
that we need food clothing shelter water
energy connection and we can create the
systems that help us get those starting
from where we are what do you currently
do for those things and how can we help
you create solutions that improve it how
can to be able to do any of this what
all of us need is information how can
create a system of information that we
trust and understand understand trust
and can actually use and so those are
the four questions that I am currently
playing around with I can envision a
platform that gives us all of that
interconnected but I don't have the
money or people to create that with so
what can we do from here what can we do
from the technology we currently have to
answer these four questions because when
I was doing my explainer video for this
channel it became very clear that that's
my journey my journey is answering these
four for me and creating the technology
to help humanity answer these four and
at every level we do it there's going to
be an upswell of energy and people
because if I could do that
for myself and more you weren't you I'm
not easily able to attract people who
are authentic and looking for their
people and have a purpose or looking for
their purpose it aligns with mine and
what we need shows up in the right time
and that is part of the journey that I'm
showcasing as well is like the weird
kismet karma stuff that happens or I
don't know what it's called just like
the stuff that happens that you can't
plan for but it's magic so that was the
four questions which again are Who am I
who are my people what is my purpose and
what do I need
it's like individual group object pretty
services and burb the duty the purpose
all right thank you